Tom Morsli Editor

Email: tommorsli@gmail.com

Address: Brayards Road, London, SE15

Mobile: 07818090527

DOB: 20/06/1996

With a particular specialism in video editing and cinematography, I have an avid interest as well as experience within the creative arts, producing freelance promotional videos alongside photography work for music festivals and live events.

Proficient in Adobe softwares Premiere Pro & Photoshop, with working knowledge in After Effects and Illustrator. Previous practice includes operating on Sony FS7, DSLRs and 35mm film cameras.

Work Experience

Kyra TV - Video Editor - December 2017 - Present. A YouTube platform producing content for Generation Z. Work as a video editor creating social media content, collaborating with big brands such as Adidas, Puma & HP.

Bluewave - Video Editor - 2017 - 2018. An underground music events company in both London and Sheffield, for whom I created a selection of online video content to promote their nights.

Call Me Mummy (48 Hour Film Project) - Video Editor - October 2017. Film was nominated for Best Ensemble and Best Sound awards for the project, with the nature of the taskrequiring incredibly quick editing in a limited amount of time.

Modual Mumbai – September 2017 – Travelled to India to collaborate alongside other UAL students and our Indian counterparts to develop projects designed to make the world a better place, of which I worked on refining ideas, branding and creating a promotional video. (Self-directed an exhibition for the trip, displayed at London College of Communication in January 2018).

Voices From Oxford - Production Assistant/Video Editor - 2015. Webcast for Oxford University's faculty, students & alumni - assisted with shoots, interviews and video editing.

StudioX1 - Production Assistant - 2014/15. Worked at the City of Oxford College's in-house production company for clients like Oxford Council, Venturefest, Oxford United and London Welsh Rugby Club.

Photography

Shooting & retouching promotional film photography for multiple live events & brands, such as:

Pretty Pretty Good (Sheffield/London) - 2016 - Ongoing Sweats (Sheffield) - 2017 - Ongoing Sunfall Festival (London) - August 2017

Soundwave Festival (Croatia) - July 2017

Examples of Work

www.vimeo.com/tmorsli www.instagram.com/morsli www.tmorsli.tumblr.com

References

Available upon request

Education

2015-18 - BA Film & Television at London College of Communication - Year 3.

2013-15 - Triple Distinction for a Level 3 Extended Diploma in Creative Media at City of Oxford College.